Register to The Leroy Anderson Papers
Yale University Music Library
- Music, Series I
  - Suite of Carols, score (49 p.) (Box 19, Folder 643)
  - Suite of Carols, score (75 p.) (Box 19, Folder 644)
  - Summer Skies Mills Music Inc., c1957; score (8 p.) & parts (Box 20, Folder 645)
    trans. Floyd E. Werle
  - Summer Skies, score (6 p.) (Box 20, Folder 646)
    Pencil. "Original score used for both recordings."
  - Summer Skies, score (10 p.) (Box 20, Folder 647)
    "Revised version used for print."
  - Summer Skies Mills Music Inc., c1954; score (5 p.) (Box 20, Folder 648)
  - Summer Skies Mills Music Inc., c1960; score (11 p.), condensed score (4 p.) & parts (Box 20, Folder 649)
  - Summer Skies (Céus de Verão) Editora Musical Mills Ltda., c1959; score (3 p.) (Box 20, Folder 650)
  - Summer Skies (sketch), condensed score (3 p.) (Box 26, Folder 899)
  - Sweet Little Jesus Boy, 2/27/49; condensed score (2 p.) (Box 20, Folder 651)
  - Sylvia, 1/23/49; condensed score (2 p.) (Box 20, Folder 652)
  - Syncopated Clock, score (12 p.) (Box 24, Folder 813)
    Ink with pencil additions. Note: (Revised) for print.
  - Syncopated Clock (Box 24, Folder 814)
    manuscripts (string parts are photocopies)
    49 parts
    Note on violin I part: Early Short version
    Envelope with notes laid in
  - Syncopated Clock, The Mills Music Inc., c1948; score (6 p.) & parts (Box 20, Folder 653)
  - Syncopated Clock, The Mills Music Inc., c1962; score (4 p.) & parts (Box 20, Folder 654)
  - Syncopated Clock, The, c1980; score (9 p.) & parts (Box 20, Folder 655)
  - Syncopated Clock, The Mills Music Inc., c1967; score (8 p.) & parts (Box 20, Folder 656)
  - Syncopated Clock, The, score (13 p.) (Box 20, Folder 657)
  - Syncopated Clock, The, score (5 p.) (Box 20, Folder 658)
    Pencil. "This is the first version, which was played as an extra at the Boston Pops on May 28, 1945. The middle section was added shortly after for publication."
  - Syncopated Clock, The Mills Music Ltd., c1951; score (3 p.) (Box 20, Folder 659)
  - Syncopated Clock, The Mills Music Ltd., c1952; parts (7 p.) (Box 20, Folder 660)
  - Syncopated Clock, The Mills Music Ltd., c1951; score (4 p.) (Box 20, Folder 661)
    arr. Harry Ralton
  - Syncopated Clock, The Mills Music Ltd., c1950; score (5 p.) (Box 20, Folder 662)
  - Syncopated Clock, The Mills Music Ltd., c1950; score (5 p.) (Box 20, Folder 663)
  - Syncopated Clock, The Toa Music Company, c1972 Columbia Music Pub. Co., Ltd.; condensed score (4 p.) & parts (Box 20, Folder 664)
  - Syncopated Clock, The Mills Music Inc., c1953; score (5 p.) (Box 20, Folder 665)
  - Syncopated Clock, The Mills Music Inc., c1957; score (5 p.) (Box 20, Folder 666)
  - Syncopated Clock, The Mills Music Inc., c1951; score (5 p.) & parts (Box 20, Folder 667)
  - Syncopated Clock, The Mills Music Inc., c1951; score (2 p.) (Box 20, Folder 668)
    Arranged for "simplified piano solo." 3 copies.
  - Syncopated Clock, The Mills Music Inc., c1951; score (3 p.) (Box 20, Folder 669)
  - Syncopated Clock, The Mills Music Inc., c1951; score (5 p.) & part (Box 20, Folder 670)
  - Syncopated Clock, The, c1981; score (7 p.) (Box 20, Folder 671)
  - Syncopated Clock, The Mills Music Inc., c1951; score (3 p.) (Box 20, Folder 672)
  - Syncopated Clock, The Mills Music Inc., c1950; score (5 p.) (Box 20, Folder 673)
  - Syncopated Clock, The Mills Music Inc., c1952; score (7 p.) (Box 20, Folder 674)
  - Syncopated Clock, The Belwin Mills/Mills Music Inc., c1950; score (5 p.) (Box 20, Folder 676)
    4 different printings.
  - Syncopated Clock, The Mills Music Inc., c1951; score (5 p.) (Box 20, Folder 677)
  - Syncopated Clock, The Mills Music Inc., c1951; score (13 p.) (Box 21, Folder 678)
  - Syncopated Clock, The Mills Music Inc., c1959; score (9 p.) (Box 21, Folder 679)
  - Syncopated Clock, The Mills Music Inc., c1951; score (8 p.) (Box 21, Folder 680)
  - Syncopated Clock, The Mills Music Inc., c1963; score (13 p.) (Box 21, Folder 681)
  - Syncopated Clock, The Mills Music Inc., c1951; score (13 p.) (Box 21, Folder 682)
  - Syncopated Clock, The Mills Music Inc., c1946; condensed score (4 p.) & parts (Box 21, Folder 683)
  - Syncopated Clock, The (O Relógio Sincopado) Editora Musical Mills Ltda., c1959; core (5 p.) (Box 20, Folder 675)
  - Tales From the Vienna Woods, 10/23/39; score (8 p.) (Box 21, Folder 684)
  - Tercentenaria, score (30 p.) (Box 21, Folder 685)
    autograph holograph
  - Tercentenaria, score (25 p.) (Box 21, Folder 686)
    "Recopied April 18, 1959"
  - Thanks a Million, score (4 p.) (Box 21, Folder 687)
  - That Moment of Moments, 1/12/36; score (5 p.) (Box 21, Folder 688)
  - The Lid's Off, score (6 p.) (Box 21, Folder 689)
  - There's a Small Hotel, score (13 p.) (Box 21, Folder 690)
  - There's Something About a Soldier, score (16 p.) (Box 21, Folder 691)
  - They Can't Write a Tune/Chop Sticks, condensed score (3 p.) (Box 21, Folder 692)
  - Thine Alone, 1/23/49; condensed score (3 p.) (Box 21, Folder 693)
  - This Is So Sudden, score (4 p.) (Box 21, Folder 694)
  - This is the Kiss of Romance, score (3 p.) (Box 21, Folder 695)
  - This is the Night, score (4 p.) (Box 21, Folder 696)
  - Thousand and One Nights, score (7 p.) (Box 21, Folder 697)
  - Through The Years, 12/26/48; condensed score (3 p.) (Box 21, Folder 698)
  - Ticonderoga March Mills Music Inc., c1945; score (12 p.) & parts (Box 21, Folder 699)
  - Tiger Medley, score (16 p.) (Box 21, Folder 700)
  - To the Hills I Lift Mine Eyes (sketch), score (1 p.) (Box 26, Folder 900)
    SATB chorus
  - Today I Feel So Happy, 12/17/33; score (1 p.) (Box 8, Folder 280)
    Pencil. Arrangement of "Happy Times" on reverse side.
  - Torna a Surriento, 2/20/1949; condensed score (3 p.) (Box 21, Folder 702)
  - Town House Maxixe Ankerford Music Corporation, 3/18/62; score (18 p.) (Box 21, Folder 703)
  - Town House Maxixe Ankerford Music Corporation, c1962; score (7 p.) (Box 21, Folder 704)
  - Tramp, Tramp, Tramp, 3/6/49; condensed score (2 p.) (Box 21, Folder 705)
  - Trees, 3/13/49; condensed score (2 p.) (Box 21, Folder 706)
  - Troika, score (4 p.) (Box 21, Folder 707)
  - Trumpeter's Lullaby, A Mills Music Inc., c1950; score (4 p.) & parts (Box 21, Folder 708)
  - Trumpeter's Lullaby, A Mills Music Inc., c1950; score (4 p.) & parts (Box 21, Folder 709)
  - Trumpeter's Lullaby, A, 9/22/49; score (13 p.) (Box 21, Folder 710)
    Copy of holograph.
  - Trumpeter's Lullaby, A Mills Music Ltd., c1950; condensed score (4 p.) & parts (Box 21, Folder 711)
  - Trumpeter's Lullaby, A Belwin Mills/Mills Music Inc., c1950 (Box 21, Folder 712)
    5 copies, various printings.
  - Trumpeter's Lullaby, A Belwin Mills/Mills Music Inc., c1962; score (4 p.) & parts (Box 21, Folder 713)
  - Trumpeter's Lullaby, A Mills Music Ltd., c1950; score (5 p.) & part (Box 21, Folder 714)
  - Trumpeter's Lullaby, A Mills Music Ltd., c1952; score (5 p.) (Box 21, Folder 715)
  - Trumpeter's Lullaby, A Mills Music Inc., c1965; condensed score (4 p.) & parts (Box 21, Folder 716)
  - Trumpeter's Lullaby, A Mills Music Ltd., c1954; condensed score/solo cornet (2 p.) & parts (Box 21, Folder 717)
  - Trumpeter's Lullaby, A Mills Music Inc., c1953; score (7 p.) (Box 21, Folder 718)
  - Trumpeter's Lullaby, A Mills Music Inc., c1952; score (5 p.) (Box 21, Folder 721)
  - Trumpeter's Lullaby, A Mills Music Inc., c1950; condensed score (4 p.) & parts (Box 21, Folder 722)
    solo trumpet & orchestra
  - Trumpeter's Lullaby, A (sketch), condensed score (4 p.) (Box 26, Folder 901)
  - Trumpeter's Lullaby, A (Trompeters Wiegenlied), c1955; score (3 p.) (Box 21, Folder 719)
  - Trumpeter's Lullaby, A (Trompeters Wiegenlied), c1955; score (3 p.) & part (Box 21, Folder 720)
  - Turn Ye To Me Mills Music Inc., c1954; score (5 p.) (Box 22, Folder 723)
  - Typewriter, The Mills Music Inc., c1954; score (8 p.) & parts (Box 22, Folder 724)
  - Typewriter, The, 10/9/50; score (17 p.) (Box 22, Folder 725)
    Penciled corrections and additions. Copy of holograph.
  - Typewriter, The Mills Music Ltd., c1953; condensed score (5 p.) & parts (Box 22, Folder 726)
  - Typewriter, The, c1981; score (7 p.) (Box 22, Folder 727)
  - Typewriter, The Belwin Mills/Mills Music Inc., c1953; score (5 p.) (Box 22, Folder 728)
  - Typewriter, The Mills Music Inc., c1953; condensed score (5 p.) & parts (Box 22, Folder 729)
  - Typewriter, The Mills Music Ltd., c1953; score (5 p.) (Box 22, Folder 731)
  - Typewriter, The (A Máquina de Escrever) Editora Musical Mills Ltda., c1959; score (5 p.) (Box 22, Folder 730)
  - Valse, La, score (11 p.) (Box 26, Folder 732)
  - Valse-Bluette/Sari Waltz, 11/4/40; score (11 p.) (Box 22, Folder 733)
  - Victory March (Lehigh), The, score (3 p.) (Box 22, Folder 734)
  - Virginia Medley, condensed score (4 p.) (Box 22, Folder 735)
  - Voices of Spring, score (9 p.) (Box 22, Folder 736)
  - Wake Up and Swing, score (10 p.) (Box 22, Folder 737)
  - Waltz of the Flowers, score (8 p.) (Box 22, Folder 738)
  - Waltz of the Flowers, score (11 p.) (Box 22, Folder 739)
  - Waltzing Cat Mills Music Ltd., c1952; score (3 p.) (Box 22, Folder 740)
    English edition for children. 3 copies.
  - Waltzing Cat Mills Music Ltd., c1951; score (4 p.) (Box 22, Folder 741)
  - Waltzing Cat Mills Music Inc., c1952; score (7 p.) (Box 22, Folder 742)
  - Waltzing Cat, The Mills Music Inc., c1958; score (19 p.) & parts (Box 22, Folder 743)
    trans. Philip J. Lang
  - Waltzing Cat, The, score (23 p.) (Box 22, Folder 744)
    Penciled additions and corrections. 2 copies of holograph.
  - Waltzing Cat, The Mills Music Ltd., c1951; score (4 p.) (Box 22, Folder 745)
  - Waltzing Cat, The Mills Music Ltd., c1951; score (5 p.) (Box 22, Folder 746)
  - Waltzing Cat, The Mills Music Inc., c1963; condensed score (4 p.) & parts (Box 22, Folder 747)
  - Waltzing Cat, The Toa Music Company, c1968 Nichion Inc.; condensed score (7 p.) & parts (Box 22, Folder 748)
  - Waltzing Cat, The Mills Music Inc., c1951; score (4 p.) & parts (Box 22, Folder 749)
  - Waltzing Cat, The Mills Music Inc., c1952; score (3 p.) (Box 22, Folder 750)
  - Waltzing Cat, The Mills Music Inc., c1951; score (4 p.) & part (Box 22, Folder 751)
  - Waltzing Cat, The Mills Music Inc., c1951; score (5 p.) (Box 22, Folder 752)
  - Waltzing Cat, The Mills Music Inc., c1951; score (5 p.) (Box 22, Folder 753)
  - Waltzing Cat, The Mills Music Inc., c1952; score (10 p.) (Box 22, Folder 754)
  - Waltzing Cat, The Mills Music Inc., c1950; condensed score (4 p.) & parts (Box 22, Folder 755)
  - Waltzing Cat, The Mills Music, Inc., c1950; vocal score (5. p.) (Box 26, Folder 902)
  - Waltzing Cat, The (O Gato Dancarino) Editora Musical Mills Ltda., c1959; score (5 p.) (Box 22, Folder 756)
  - Waltzing Cat, The (sketch), vocal score (6. p.) (Box 26, Folder 903)
  - Waltzing Cat, The (sketch), condensed score (6 p.) (Box 26, Folder 904)
  - Wanting You, 2/20/1949; condensed score (3 p.) (Box 22, Folder 757)
  - Water Music (sketch), [2] p. of music (Box 24, Folder 815)
  - Wearing of the Green, The, score (24 p.) (Box 22, Folder 759)
  - Wearing of the Green, The (sketch), condensed score (5 p.) (Box 26, Folder 905)
  - Welt Schlager für Akkordeon Band 8 Mills Musikverlag et al., c1952; score (24 p.) (Box 22, Folder 760)
    voice & accordion
    Collection of 11 arrangements including Anderson's "Blue Tango." German edition.
  - Welt Schlager für Akkordeon Band 9 Mills Musikverlag et al., c1952; score (27 p.) (Box 22, Folder 761)
    arr. Bruno Schlosser
  - We're Going Home to Get to Know Our Mothers, condensed score (3 p.) (Box 22, Folder 758)
  - West Point Alma Mater, score (1 p.) (Box 22, Folder 762)
  - What a Wonderful World, score (4 p.) (Box 22, Folder 763)
  - What's on the Penny, 11/4/40; score (11 p.) (Box 22, Folder 764)
    Pencil. "for Ruby Newman."
  - When I Hear Music, score (4 p.) (Box 22, Folder 765)
  - When I Hear Music (Overture), score (2 p.) (Box 22, Folder 766)
  - Where Am I?, score (4 p.) (Box 23, Folder 767)
  - Whiffenpoof Song, 4/3/49; condensed score (3 p.) (Box 23, Folder 768)
  - Who Am I to Say, score (3 p.) (Box 23, Folder 769)
  - Who's Been Sitting in My Chair?, score (15 p.) & vocal part (Box 23, Folder 770)
  - Wiener Blut, score (11 p.) (Box 23, Folder 771)
  - Wine, Women, and Song, score (13 p.) (Box 23, Folder 772)
  - Wintergreen, condensed score (4 p.), trumpet parts on separate sheet (Box 23, Folder 773)
  - Wintergreen for President, score (9 p.) (Box 23, Folder 774)
  - With a Song, 12/19/48; (3 p.) (Box 23, Folder 775)
    in my Heart
  - Without a Song (Great Day), 12/12/48; (2 p.) (Box 23, Folder 776)
  - Wolf, score (2 p.) (Box 23, Folder 777)
  - World of Our Own, (1 p.) (Box 23, Folder 778)
    Rand Smith
    vocal trio
  - Write What You Feel, (1 p.) (Box 23, Folder 779)
  - Yale Medley, score (1 p.) (Box 23, Folder 780)
  - Yale Medley, score (5 p.) & parts (Box 23, Folder 781)
  - Yale Potpourri, 5/6/48; score (9 p.) (Box 23, Folder 782)
    Pencil. "First performance May 10, 1948."
  - You Are Love, 12/12/48; condensed score (3 p.) (Box 23, Folder 783)
  - You Can Always Tell (sketch), condensed score (2 p.) (Box 26, Folder 907)
  - You Can Always Tell a Harvard Man: Hommage à Richard Bissell (sketch), vocal score (4 p.) (Box 26, Folder 906)
    words by John Witherspoon
  - You'll Have to Swing It, score (2 p.) (Box 23, Folder 784)
  - You'll Never Know Romance, condensed score (2 p.) (Box 23, Folder 785)
  - Young Man's Fancy, score (1 p.) & parts (Box 23, Folder 786)
  - Yours Is My Heart Alone, 3/6/49; condensed score (3 p.) (Box 23, Folder 787)
  - Yours Truly Is Truly Yours, 1/4/36; score (4 p.) (Box 23, Folder 788)
  - Zigeuner, condensed score (1 p.) (Box 23, Folder 789)
    Pencil. Attached to "Society Rag."
  - Zulu Lulu, score (4 p.) (Box 23, Folder 790)
- Miscellaneous, Series II
  - Goldilocks script, typescript (86 p.) (Box 33, Folder 909)
    Pencilled additions and corrections
  - Goldilocks script, typescript (45 p.) (Box 33, Folder 910)
    Corrections to script 33/905
  - Goldilocks script, c1955; typescript (124 p.) (Box 33, Folder 911)
  - Goldilocks script, c1956; typescript (129 p.) (Box 33, Folder 912)
  - Goldilocks script, c1956; typescript (129 p.) (Box 33, Folder 913)
  - Goldilocks script, typescript (22 p.) (Box 33, Folder 914)
    Corrections to other scripts?
  - Peoples' Composer: The Story of Leroy Anderson and Those Around Him, by George Wright Briggs, Jr., typescript (276 p.) (Box 33, Folder 915)
  - Leroy Anderson Catalog of Works [appendix 1], typescript (7 p.) (Box 33, Folder 916)
  - Chronological List of Decca Sessions [appendix 2], typescript (4 p.) (Box 33, Folder 916)
  - Chronological Discography of Leroy Anderson's Works as recorded by Arthur Fiedler and the Boston Pops Orchestra [appendix 3A], typescript (1 p.) (Box 33, Folder 916)
  - Alphabetical Discography of Leroy Anderson's Works as recorded by Arthur Fiedler [appendix 3B], typescript (1 p.) (Box 33, Folder 916)
  - The Music of Leroy Anderson Published by Mills Music [appendix 4], photocopy of published catalog (6 p.) (Box 33, Folder 916)
  - Leroy Anderson 1980 Discography [appendix 5], typescript (5 p.) (Box 33, Folder 916)
  - Biographical sketch of Leroy Anderson prepared by Eleanor Anderson, typescript (4 p.) (Box 33, Folder 917)
  - Press releases and newspaper clippings, 1959-1988; (11 p.) (Box 33, Folder 918)
  - MSS 61/II/scrapbooks, 4 scrapbooks on microfilm